Short Bio of Dr. Doo Yong Park



Dr. Park was appointed as the President of Korea Occupational Safety and Health Agency (KOSHA) on 27th December 2017 for 3 years. He was the Professor at the Department of Mechanical Systems Engineering, Hansung University but he temporarily stopped his academic research and teaching to move to the KOSHA

Professional Experience

Dr. Park had been the Director General of the KOSHA Research Institute for 2006-2008. He was the Immediate Past-President of the International Occupational Hygiene Association (IOHA; 2016-2017) and the Korean Industrial Hygiene Association (KIHA; 2015-2017).

Over the past decades, he has been working together with Hygienist from many Asian countries such as Malaysia, Indonesia, Singapore, Vietnam and India for the development and enhancement of Industrial Hygiene in various ways. He was a member of the International Advisory Panel (IAP) to the Ministry of Manpower, Singapore. He has played a key role in establishing the Asian Network of Occupational Hygiene (ANOH) and served himself as the President from 2014 to 2017.

Education

Dr. Park graduated from School of Public Health, Seoul National University and received his Doctoral degree from the School of Public Health, University of Michigan, U.S. He is one of the pioneers in the history of Occupational Hygiene in South Korea.

Awards

Dr. Park won the 'Warren Cook Award' as he graduated at the top of the School of Public Health, University of Michigan in 1996. And he also received the 'Best Thesis Award' at KOSHA in 2015.